# **BRETT**



# www.builtbygoat.com

### **Summary**

I am an Army veteran with experience in B2B sales, web development, and intelligence analysis. I have a Bachelor of Science in International Management, with Economics and Honors Minors. Lastly, I am self-taught in HTML5, CSS3, and other web languages.

#### Technical Skills

## Advanced (2+ Years)

HTML5, CSS3 (and their predecessors), Front-end frameworks (such as Bootstrap, Foundation, Skeleton, etc), Command Line, and Git version control.

# **Intermediate (1-2 Years)**

Javascript, jQuery, AngularJS, and PHP. Network mapping and installation, as well as basic systems administration on Windows-based devices.

# **Basic (0 – 1 Year)**

HandlebarsJS, MySQL, MongoDB, Ruby/Rails, Python, NodeJS, and Java. Search Engine Optimization and website performance management.

That's it! ... Well, no it isn't. You can read the second page for the hard bits. (But we both know, that stuff is boring.)

I want to be *your* junior UX/developer on the front-end. I have a passion for tweaking things to make them more *useable* and *beautiful*. If you want someone who strives to *learn*, *adapt*, and is *energetic*, I am your person.







#### Honors

#### **AppNeta**

- Brought in \$10,000 in sales within first two months.
- Brought in \$50,000 in sales within six months.
- Promoted within first three months.

#### **Delta Sigma Pi**

- Xi Phi Chapter Collegiate of the Year from 2011 2013.
- New England Region Collegiate of the Year in 2013.

#### **US Army**

- Joint Meritorious Unit Award in 2009.
- Afghanistan Campaign Ribbon with Campaign Star in 2009.
- Army Good Conduct Medal in 2009.
- Army Commendation Medal in 2009.
- Army Achievement Medal in 2007.
- Global War on Terrorism Expeditionary Ribbon in 2006.

#### **Experience**

#### **AppNeta**

#### **September 2014 - May 2015**

#### **Business Development Representative II**

Proactively developed a Sales Binder to help develop sales skills. Develop prospect pool for Account Executives. Scripted in Selenium to test prospects' web applications. Produced web performance reports to aid Sales Executives.

#### **Delta Sigma Pi**

#### August 2011 - December 2013

#### Xi Phi Chapter President

Reinvigorated membership activity Increased footprint on campus. Developed partnerships with corporate organizations. Planned and coordinated multiple professional and academic events. Hosted events, providing access to college students for professional organizations and speakers. Hosted speakers and provided access to corporate tours of State Street for students. Formed inter-organizational partnerships, brought together other campus organizations to participate in multiple events, helped promote other organizations events

#### **US Army**

#### July 2006 - July 2010

#### **Human Intelligence Collections Specialist**

Deployed to Afghanistan in support of U.S. Army Special Forces. Interrogated foreign detainees while following legal guidelines and procedures. Collected and analyzed intelligence, while managing multiple intelligence sources. Conducted and taught biometrics assessments to help produce threat assessments. Ran jail operations within legal guidelines and procedures. Maintained local internet networks and managed local computer equipment. Held certification in vehicle operations, generator operations, and unit armorer. Certified by IRS as a tax preparer and quality control specialist.

#### Education

#### **University of Massachusetts Boston**

2011 - 2014

**Bachelor of Science (BS), International Management** 

International Fraternity of Delta Sigma Pi. Sigma Alpha Pi Honors Society. UMass Boston Honors College Minor. Economics Minor. Deans' List.